И первый приз уходит…
Выступавшей под номером 3!
Сакурагаоке Нанами-сан!
Спасибо вам большое!
Я буду стараться изо всех сил, чтобы стать ещё лучше.
Спасибо вам всем!
Она невероятна.
Нам треба работать швидче, тэж.
Да… Нам, как её наставникам,
предстоит многому её обучить.
А разве мы можем её чему-то научить?
Конечно, можем!
У нас второй сезон «Кусурэ» на носу.
Наоборот, не будет
преувеличением сказать,
что мы на вершине этого бизнесса.
Може наоборот, може нет,
але ти преувеличиваешь.
Я просто пытаюсь сказать Яэ,
что нужно быть более уверенной.
Потому что, как сэйю, мы уже наставники!
#09「Обеспокоенная Титосэ и Неудержимый Новобранец」
Холодно! Холодно!
Едва успела прямо к началу?
И как долго ты планировала спать?
Всё в порядке, Годзё-кун. Как говорится…
«Выспавшийся малыш — счастливый малыш»
Просто, взгляни на общую картину
и ты увидишь, как я постепенно расту.
Ты кем себя возомнила,
с такими речами?
Доброе утро.
Мокотяка
Властитель Цзюлуна и
Тысячелетняя принцесса
Доброе утро.
Приятно, снова, иметь с вами дело.
Мне так жаль. Этот дрянной п~
Т.е., наш продюссер, Кудзу,
работает сегодня допоздна.
В худшем случае, он может не появиться вообще.
Мне очень жаль.
Он, только что, обозвал его чем-то стра~
Всё в порядке, но разве это отодвинет время начала?
А, нет. С этим всё в порядке.
Можете считать, что Кудзу мёртв,
и начинать без него.
Х-Хорошо…
Ну, надеюсь на продуктивную работу.
Только первая серия, а этот муд~
т.е. Кудзу-сан не прийдёт?
Ну, уже второй сезон.
Точно. Второй сезон
тайтла, который не продался.
Не мели, что попало, без разрешения.
Когда озвучиваешь,
старайся читать между строк.
Хорошо.
Зритель разбежался
И продюссер тоже.
Но мы зашли за черту,
Нам никто не поможет.
Разрешите… Можно вас на минутку?
Да, спасибо вам.
Чтобы ты просила исходники.
Такая редкость.
Конечно, я спрашиваю. Это моя работа.
Ты хотела сказать — наша работа.
Экхм…
Всем приветы. Мы сегодня пришли осмотреться.
Надеюсь на сотрудничество.
О, начальник!
Как насчёт партейки?
Нельзя. Нельзя. Я всё ещё на работе.
Но, босс, Май Май-тян,
любящей аниме, так одиноко.
Но, они же просто баклуши пинают,
если меня нет на месте.
Товада? Мужик, у меня тут завал!
Я задержусь часа на три. Я буду уже немного…
А? Уже всё? Вы, парни, уже выпиваете?
Ну, то есть, без меня вечеринка не будет…
Никто ничего не сказал?
А, хорошо… Приду, как будет время.
Ты сказал, Май Май-тян сегодня здесь?
Дамы и господа,
спасибо за то, что пришли сегодня,
несмотря на плотный график.
В любом случае, так приятно, снова,
работать со всеми вами, начиная с этой недели.
Ура!
Всем здрасте.
Спасибо, что пришли сегодня.
Спасибо вам всем огромное!
Я сегодня так много узнала.
Ой, нет! Дайте я.
Не, не, не…
Ты не должна…
Я делаю это ещё и ради моего отца.
Навевает воспоминания.
Помниться, была такой же.
У тебя было высокое положение, с самого начала.
Вычислила меня?
Добрэ.
Не за что. Я ж новенькая,
так что в порядке вещей.
Не стоит быть такой формальной.
Хоча, иногда, круто, коли, в агентстве,
есть хтось моложе тоби.
Кото-тян, разве, ты не была всегда самой старой?
Хм?
А, нет, ничего…
Кохай, да… Классное чувство.
О-да. Теперь, я чувствую,
что нужно стараться ещё сильнее.
Нанами-тян, если что-нибудь понадобиться,
дай мне знать.
Да, я сделаю всё, что в моих силах.
Ваша забота — это честь для меня, сэнпай.
«Сэнпай»… Как же приятно звучит.
Я не уверена, достойны ли мы этого звания.
Ведь, то були наши перши главные роли.
Н-Ну, мы всё ещё в процессе становления.
Возможно, сегодня, ты впервые увидела нас в действии,
но, в будущем, это будет бесценный опыт…
Ой, не впервые!
Это… Я смотрела все серии «Кусурэ».
Карасума-сан, твой крик
за Юну в 5 серии был хорош.
О? Правда? Ты смотрела?
Да. Я прочитала всё оригинальное ранобэ,
поэтому я очень взволнована, увидев моих
любимых персонажей вживую.
О-хо! Так ты была поражена
непревзойдённым мастерством озвучки
Золушки, Карасумы Титосэ-тян,
заодно продавшей 10,000 CD?
Да! Я решилась на прослушивание лишь потому,
что была вдохновлена вами, Карасума-сэнпай!
Хвала небесам, что смогла вас встретить!
Вот как! Было бы неплохо,
если мы будем иногда пересекаться.
Т. е., раз у нас две Золушки вместе,
всё будет в кожуре.
Ты просто поразительна, Карасума-сан!
Вах! Вах! Вах! Ти-сама, тоби не стоит…
Вы хорошо поладили,
но, совершенно, не в ту степь.
Титосэ, серьёзно…
Пркрати нести эту чепухню!
Эт потому, шт ты говоришь о вещах,
на которых застряла сама, э!
Ч-Чеп…?
Чеп… Чепухню?
Добрэ, Кадзуха-сама, твий акцент
знову наружу вилиз.
Кото-тян, твой, тоже, рвётся наружу!
Иногда, твой привычный говор проскальзывает.
Как я, когда, временами, называю
Годзё-куна «Менеджером».
Это абсолютная правда…
Это не имеет значения.
Откуда родом твоя семья?
Ибараки? Ямагата?
Я всё ещё не получила сувениров из той поездки.
Сувениры тут не при чём!
Причина в тебе!
Теперь есть кто-то, дебютировавший после тебя.
Ты больше не можешь называться новичком.
Ты уже оформившийся профессионал.
Пора всерьёз задуматься над этим.
Ясно…
Ты точно поняла, о чём я?
Да, Сибасаки-сан…
О. Полагаю, теперь могу звать тебя «Кадзуха-тян».
Я, тип, поняла, что ты мне хотела
донести, Кадзуха-тян.
Ч-Что с тобо…
Вот, ты, наконец, разглядела, кто я есть на самом деле.
С-Серьёзно, ты это не совсем так поняла!
Вот именно, Титосэ.
Ты должна внимательнее слушать её.
Чепухня рассуждает о твоём будущем
своим чепухнёвым способом.
Прекрати повторять «чепухня».
Ой, да ладно, Чепухня.
Накатика ещё, Чепухня.
Вот это понимаю северянка.
Оформившийся профессионал, да…
I mean, I'm a legitimate pro,
so I gave the committee a piece of my mind.
I bet you did!
I mean, entertainment isn't about numbers.
I had no idea.
Yeah, only people who are actually working
on the project understand these things…
That's amazing!
Nah… I mean, it's only natural for me,
since I see everything as entertainment.
Since you're here, why don't
we have another bottle?
Hm? Oh, sure.
That's why I love you, Кудзу-сан!
Oh, really? Well, I am pretty loaded.
Really? That's an anime producer for you!
You love anime, don't you, Май Май-тян?
Maybe I'll bring a voice actor with me next time.
Really?
What anime do you like, by the way?
Let's see…
Out of the ones I've seen recently,
there's this,
and this…
I see, I see…
Титосэ! What do you think about it?
Good question…
You changin' the subject?
Shibasaki-сан, let's drink something else.
U-Um…
I heard you talking… Is it
true that you liked «Кусурэ»?
Yes! I have the first press for each volume.
I'm collecting all the store bonuses, too.
I see. I'm sure Sensei will be happy to hear that.
What did you think of the anime?
It was great!
Oh, come on. There must be something
more you'd like to say about it.
No!
I really, really love «Кусурэ»,
so I really enjoyed watching every episode.
I-I see…
But if there was one thing…
One thing?
I wish a lot more people had watched it.
«Кусурэ» is so good.
I hope that
more people are able to see that.
Yeah…
I'm truly blessed today for being
able to see behind the scenes
and meet so many people
involved with «Кусурэ».
I…
will continue to work even harder!
We need to put in the work
to make a great series
and regain the viewers that we lost.
I think it'd be better to create a buzz
with something new and
reach an unknown crowd.
The anime and original story sides
need to work together…
Um… I'll participate in even more events.
Not just the handout events,
but something else…
Yeah, but the agency has
their own responsibilities,
so we can't really make
that decision on our own.
Oh, right…
But we would all like to do whatever we can.
Right, Кадзуха–sama?
Heck yeah!
Are you guys talking about
something fun? Let me join.
Where did she…
I-I-I ate way too much… Годзё-кун!
We're going to change
how we do the radio show?
Yes. We've been doing it
after the dubbing sessions,
but there were a lot of limitations.
So now we're going to work
with various shops to record it.
But will all of our schedules line up?
Well, we'll probably have to make
some adjustments here and there…
We'll just have to work it out step by step.
Uh, and where will we be going?
That's being worked out.
We thought it'd be good
to throw out some ideas.
I see…
Is this another one of Кудзу-сан's ideas?
Ah… No…
But we've gotten permission,
so everything is fine.
Okay…
Official Channel
Broadcasting Live
User
Broadcast
Broadcast Live
By Popularity
Millennium Princess x Kowloon
Overlord KusuRadio
Official Channel
Broadcasting Live
User
Broadcast
Broadcast Live
By Popularity
Millennium Princess x Kowloon
Overlord KusuRadio
All right, we're going to start the test.
We're ready.
Is the trash… I mean, Кудзу-сан here yet?
Ah, no, he's running behind with other work,
so he said he'll come if he can.
I mean, if we can just go through you,
Товада-сан, that works, too.
No, I don't think that's good.
I just hope Кудзу-сан feels more
motivated to show up here…
Yeah, that's not happening.
He wasn't always trash.
He was famous for working really hard
before he came to our agency.
So I keep believing that he'll
help us out in the end…
It was great back in the day!
If we released DVDs, they sold.
So you were really amazing!
But streaming is being
killed by illegal uploads,
so the business scheme has changed.
I see.
So anyway, it's almost my birthday!
Where's Май Май-тян?
Oh, sorry.
Looks like someone else picked her today.
Oh, come on, Сякудзии-сан.
You're going to drink more, aren't you?
I love when you're like that.
Do you know each other?
He's a former coworker who
started at the same time I did.
Кудзу quit the company
and got a different job,
but I'm still with the company.
And you can see the difference between us.
I could hear your voice
from all the way over there.
You never change.
You still haven't grown up.
Could I get my check, please?
Where are you going?
I'm going to drink somewhere else.
You're running away again?
Huh?
Just like you lost to me
at work and ran away…
Are you running away again here?
What did you say?
You used to have more of a backbone.
Hey, Сякудзии-сан, let's hurry
back so we can drink more.
Should we have Dom? Or Peri?
Wait just a moment, okay?
Oh, please! I'll wait as long as you want!
You're always like that…
You steal everything from me…
promotions, women,
and now the oasis for my soul.
What are you going to do about it?
I'm going to win this time!
And then I'm going to get
my Май Май-тян back!
I don't belong to you, Кудзу-сан.
I know that!
Damn it! Damn it!
Ow…
Hey.
Damn it…
Hello, Кудзу-сан? Where are you?
Товада, save me!
The second installment of
that major hit anime!
The role of a lifetime has arrived.
I've already won!
I have no idea what makes you
think you'll pass that audition.
Not to mention, there's a limit of
one person per role per agency.
Which means?
We have to limit how many people audition.
I see. That sucks for everyone else.
What makes you think
you're going to be the one?
It's almost my birthday,
so that'd be the perfect present.
Are you the center of the world?
Oh, about that…
Talent Profile
Name: Сакурагаока Нанами
Reading: Сакурагаока Нанами
Birthday: 4/7
Birthplace: Tokyo
Dialect: None
Hobbies: Living a well-balanced life
Skills: Softball
Full Name (Birth Name): Сакурагаока Нанами
Birthday: 4/7
Надпись: Aries
Blood Type: O
Age 18 (Actual age can be disclosed)
Birthplace: Tokyo
Address: Chofu City, Tokyo
Family: Lives at home with her mother and father. An only child.
We want her to audition.
Huh?
Sir, that's not what we discussed…
This matter is…
I'm sorry!
But after seeing her at the party the
other day, I felt she could do it.
The party? Do what?
I mean, Титосэ-кун
started out the same way.
Don't we want her to take
flight like Титосэ-кун has?
Huh? U-Um, I…
Well, with Титосэ-кун,
I think it's about time she takes
the next step and tries for \Нанамиrration and foreign film dubs.
H-Huh?!
Yep, yep, yep.
No, no, no, no…
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
No, no, no, no, no!
Yep, yep, yep!
No, no, yep…?
Yep, yep, yep?
No way…
Sir, that's not possible.
Титосэ isn't even secure with anime as it is…
Годзё-кун… You're exactly right.
And that's exactly why!
Титосэ-кун and Нанами-тян
will both be our poster girls!
What I'm saying is…
Just try to remember, Годзё-кун…
When you were a voice actor,
you got a lead role around this time.
The youth have every right to dream,
and it's our duty to sell them that dream.
And so, Годзё-кун, you'll be in charge
of the new girl from now on.
I expect the best from you,
our most capable Манаger!
Huh? Годзё-кун is going to be
both my Манаger and Нанами's?
Oh, no. We'll get you a different
tactful Манаger, Титосэ-кун.
You'll have your own Манаger!
A different… But that's…
Yep, yep!
Number One Produce will keep
moving toward the future
on even more solid footing!
Good morning.
Oh… Yeah.
Sorry, I got called away suddenly,
so let's talk another time.
I'm home.
You're home late. Did you
have a lot to talk about?
It was late, so I made
sure she got home safe.
She's still in high school.
Huh…
More importantly, why are you
dressed like that? You'll catch a cold.
That's sexual harassment!
A Манаger is sexually harassing an idol!
This is a huge scandal that'll
Сякудзииe the whole industry!
This means he'll have to lose all of his
current charges, doesn't it,
Commentator Карасума-сан?
It's not going to Сякудзииe the industry,
and you're not an idol to begin with.
I should be a worthy commodity
to market as an idol.
Do you not understand my worth, Годзё-кун?
You don't have any worth.
I wonder if the agency has
any plans to market me.
I think they need to reconsider my Манаger.
You really are trash for switching
the blame onto the agency.
You're not even in charge
of me anymore, Годзё-кун!
You sold your soul to the evil agency!
Quit making stupid false accusations.
Stupid? It's not stupid…
You've got it easy, Годзё-кун.
You have a job where you don't have to do
anything and still get paid every month.
That was my decision.
The same goes for you. You chose this.
Yeah, but…
I didn't! I didn't!
At this rate, I might end up
quitting as a voice actor
after just having one lead role,
just like you, Годзё-кун.
You're not answering that?
Yes.
Hello! Um,
thank you so much for everything today.
Preview
Годзё-сан, I'll try to work even harder.
I'll put effort first, second, third,
fourth, all the way to a hundred!
If I don't work hard,
it'll be rude to Карасума-сан.
Huh? Oh, you think so?
Карасума-сан's really amazing!
Well, I also think that if she'd just—
She's cute, confident,
and completely transparent!
Oh, right…
I want to be like Карасума-сан!
Please, no. One Карасума
Титосэ is more than enough.